<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contexts>
	<context id="review_wizard_page_context" title="Review Wizard Page">
		<description>
		The semi-formal proof review wizard presents each proof statement for
		review within its justification context.  Choose a statement on the left-hand
		side of the page to view its details on the right-hand side.  Use the
		validation buttons on the details page to assign a validation type to each
		statement.  
		</description>
		<topic href="html/topics/review_page.html" label="Review Wizard Page" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_wizard.html" label="Review Wizard" />
		<topic href="html/concepts/sfp.html" label="Semi-Formal Proof" />
	</context>
	<context id="review_wizard_proof_context" title="Semi-Formal Proof Page">
		<description>
		The proof details page presents the theorem-level statement of the proof.  
		This page shows the justifications for the proof, which are the inferences
		or deductions made in the context of other statements.    
		</description>
		<topic href="html/topics/review_proof.html" label="Review Wizard Proof" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_page.html" label="Review Wizard Page" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_statement.html" label="Review Wizard Statement" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_wizard.html" label="Review Wizard" />
		<topic href="html/concepts/sfp.html" label="Semi-Formal Proof" />
	</context>
	<context id="review_wizard_statement_context" title="Semi-Formal Statement Page">
		<description>
		The statement details page presents the argument-body statements of the proof.
		The page shows the details for the statement selected in the proof navigator
		pane.  According to the structure of the statement, the page will show the
		statement's premises, inferences, entailments, and deductions.  At the bottom
		of the page use the validation buttons to assign a valid, invalid, or unknown
		state (along with the author and time stamp records) to the statement
		if the items shown together justify the statement.       
		</description>
		<topic href="html/topics/review_proof.html" label="Review Wizard Proof" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_page.html" label="Review Wizard Page" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_hypothesis.html" label="Review Wizard Hypothesis" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_wizard.html" label="Review Wizard" />
		<topic href="html/concepts/sfp.html" label="Semi-Formal Proof" />
	</context>
	<context id="review_wizard_hypothesis_context" title="Semi-Formal Hypothesis Page">
		<description>
		An hypothesis statement page presents a proof statement that serves as
		an unjustified-hypothesis.  Consequently, the unrelated justification areas
		contain no other supporting information.  This is merely a special case
		of a statement. The page shows the statement selected in the proof navigator
		pane, and the comment column shows the 'hypothesis' key word.  At the bottom
		of the page use the validation buttons to assign a valid, invalid, or unknown
		state (along with the author and time stamp records) to the statement
		if the hypothesis is reasonable.       
		</description>
		<topic href="html/topics/review_proof.html" label="Review Wizard Proof" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_page.html" label="Review Wizard Page" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_statement.html" label="Review Wizard Statement" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_wizard.html" label="Review Wizard" />
		<topic href="html/concepts/sfp.html" label="Semi-Formal Proof" />
	</context>
	<context id="review_wizard_setup_context" title="Review Wizard Setup Page">
		<description>
		The semi-formal proof (SFP) review wizard's first page prompts for some setup information to be
		applied on the subsequent pages.  The prompts for author and time stamp
		refer to the validation records that the wizard will then assign to each
		validation action taken by the analyst using the wizard.  When the analyst
		validates or invalidates a statement on the subsequent page, the wizard
		will record that choice along with the author and time stamp in the validation
		record for the statement.  These can be seen in the wizard as well as in
		the SFP editor.  The buttons on this page are convenience tools to clear
		earlier records and start over; the wizard will prompt to acknowledge each
		of these button actions.  
		</description>
		<topic href="html/topics/review_page.html" label="Review Wizard Page" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_statement.html" label="Review Wizard Statement" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_proof.html" label="Review Wizard Proof" />
		<topic href="html/topics/review_wizard.html" label="Review Wizard" />
		<topic href="html/concepts/sfp.html" label="Semi-Formal Proof" />
	</context>
	
</contexts>
