<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="net.certware.feature.planning"
      label="CertWare Project Planning Support"
      version="1.2.3.qualifier"
      provider-name="Kestrel Technology LLC"
      license-feature="net.certware.feature"
      license-feature-version="1.2.3.qualifier">

   <description url="http://nasa.github.com/CertWare">
      CertWare support for project planning using a DSL for planning notation.  Requires the ARM feature.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2011 United States Government as represented by
the National Aeronautics and Space Administration.  All rights
reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://nasa.github.com/CertWare/license.html">
      Copyright (c) 2011 United States Government as represented by
the National Aeronautics and Space Administration.  All rights
reserved.
This use of this software is governed by the CertWare Safety
Case Workbench BETA-TEST AGREEMENT OF EXPERIMENTAL COMPUTER CODE.
Use of this software is limited to beta-testing only.  No modifications
to the software or further development of the software are permitted.
This software incorporates open source software.  Such open source
software is identified via notices within the source code.  Such
notices identify the governing open source license and use of
such open source software is governed by the terms and conditions
of the governing open source license.  NASA disclaims all warranties
and liabilities regarding open source software and distributes
it &quot;as is&quot; under this Agreement.
This software shall not be exported outside the United Kingdom,
except to the United States, without the express permission of
NASA. Access to the SOFTWARE within the United Kingdom to TESTER’s
organization is permitted for United Kingdom, Canadian, Greek
and U.S. persons only.  Furthermore, the software shall not be
provided to any person or entity listed on any U.S. &quot;denied parties/persons&quot;
list (including the U.S. Department of the Treasury, Office of
Foreign Assets Control, Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked
Persons; U.S. Department of the Treasury, Office of Foreign Assets
Control, Changes to List of Specially Designated Nationals and
Blocked Persons; U.S. Department of State, Directorate of Defense
Trade Controls, List of Statutorily Debarred Parties; U.S. Department
of Commerce, Bureau of Industry and Security, Denied Persons
List; U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of Industry and Security,
Entity List).  Violations may result in criminal liability under
U.S. laws.
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY
KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED, IMPLIED, OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL CONFORM TO
SPECIFICATIONS, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS
FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND FREEDOM FROM INFRINGEMENT, AND
ANY WARRANTY THAT THE DOCUMENTATION WILL CONFORM TO THE SOFTWARE,
OR ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE ERROR FREE, WHETHER
OR NOT THE ERROR IS DISCOVERABLE.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE UNITED
STATES GOVERNMENT, OR ITS CONTRACTORS OR SUBCONTRACTORS, BE LIABLE
FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DIRECT, INDIRECT,
SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF, RESULTING FROM,
OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THIS SOFTWARE, WHETHER OR NOT BASED
UPON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT , OR OTHERWISE, WHETHER OR NOT
INJURY WAS SUSTAINED BY PERSONS OR PROPERTY OR OTHERWISE, WHETHER
OR NOT DAMAGES ARE BASED ON A THIRD PARTY CLAIM, WHETHER OR NOT
LOSS WAS SUSTAINED FROM, OR AROSE OUT OF THE RESULTS OF, OR USE
OF, THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICES PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND REGARDLESS
OF WHETHER THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT SHALL BE ADVISED, SHALL
HAVE OTHER REASON TO KNOW, OR IN FACT SHALL KNOW OF THE POSSIBILITY
OF THE FOREGOING.  THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT DISCLAIMS ALL
WARRANTIES AND LIABILITIES REGARDING THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, IF
PRESENT IN THE NASA GENERATED SOFTWARE, AND DISTRIBUTES IT ‘AS
IS.
USE OF THIS SOFTWARE IS AN AGREEMENT TO WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS
AGAINST THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT, AND ITS CONTRACTORS AND
SUBCONTRACTORS, AND TO  INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS THE UNITED
STATES GOVERNMENT AND ITS CONTRACTORS AND SUBCONTRACTORS FOR
ANY LIABILITIES, DEMANDS, DAMAGES, EXPENSES OR LOSSES THAT MAY
BE INCURRED FROM USE OF THIS SOFTWARE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="CertWare" url="https://github.com/nasa/CertWare/raw/master/net.certware.feature.updatesite"/>
      <discovery label="CertWare" url="http://github.com/nasa/CertWare/update"/>
   </url>

   <includes
         id="net.certware.feature"
         version="0.0.0"
         search-location="both"/>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.osgi"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.util"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.common"/>
      <import plugin="org.antlr.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.log4j"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xpand"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtend"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.mwe.utils"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtend.typesystem.emf"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.navigator"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.jobs"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.swt"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.ui.shared"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.builder"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.edit"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.edit.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.codegen.ecore.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore.xmi"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.cpn"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.cpn.generator"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.cpn.navigator"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.cpn.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.cpn.view"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.mspdi"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.mspdi.edit"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.certware.planning.mspdi.editor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
